WOLOWITZ:
So, how does this game work?
(Howard:)I just throw it,
like a real ball?
(Leonard:)Yeah, just nice and easy,
right over the plate.
(Howard:)All right.
(Man in Crowd:)You suck, Wolowitz!
(Howard:)What's that about?
(Raj:)I'm heckling you.
(Raj:)It's a beloved part
of baseball.
SHELDON:
He's right.
(Sheldon:)And given that you're
probably still waiting
(Sheldon:)to be picked for a game that
was played in fifth grade,
(Sheldon:)I'm sure you do suck.
(Penny:)Hi. What's going on?
(Raj:)Baseball.
(Penny:)Okay, this is not
what I meant when I said
(Penny:)go outside and play.
(Leonard:)He's practicing.
(Penny:)For what?
(Howard:)The Angels wanted an astronaut
(Howard:)to throw out the first pitch,
(Howard:)so guess who they called?
What, you? Really?!
(Howard:)Well, a lot of people who
weren't available, but then me!
That's so cool!
(Penny:)Congratulations.
(Penny:)I guess that makes you
the athlete of the group.
Well, not just him!
(Sheldon:)May I remind you that you're
talking to the seeker, beater,
(Sheldon:)chaser and water boy
(Sheldon:)of the third place
Griffith Park Quidditch team.
(Penny:)I know.
(Penny:)Watching your boyfriend
run around with a broomstick
(Penny:)between his legs
isn't something you forget.
(Leonard:)C'mon now,
throw one.
(Howard:)All right,
here we go.
You look like a jackass!
Cut it out!
You're hurting my feelings!
(Leonard:)Now you know why
we're not outside.